I'm super strong, super strong, super strong
It's a nice morning though
But today in the morning, can I do makeup for Ha-chan?
Ah, thank you very much
thank you
Yesterday, I became really good friends with people from another group.
I was with other groups the whole time.
was talking
fun
Which number would you prefer?
This is Sakai number 46.
This is Yoshikawa number 49.
This is Meat Yoshikawa
I want to eat meat.
Okay
Of course I've never done it like this.
Using the floor like this
That guy please
yes
That's amazing
shortly
أIndividual
Is it because I won't drop it anymore?
Why do you think it's scary?
I want you to keep pointing at me
It won't last long
Mix it up, raise your hand if you have a secret too
If you want to get closer to me, open your hand
thank you
Thank you everyone
Ah, there it was!
cute!
Can I get this below?
What should I do?
Should I do it this way?
Look forward to it
What should I do?
Thank you for watching
Number 1 is like this, number 2 is like this.
Does that mean you start facing left?
Yeah.
Start facing left.
Sorry, but I've put on my costume.
mosaic.
It's really bad.
shed mosaic.
It's good for your skin.
No make-up.
I agree.
5 minutes before the start of the pro.
on second thoughts
My current father
My father
Looks like it's rough
Ah, I see.
me now
I was the head of Konata
last
first
It's the first
Maybe tomorrow
part of me
2nd show tomorrow
1st performance tomorrow
2nd performance
There are two songs that will be performed in full.
That's dangerous
Moreover, both songs are not dances that you would normally dance to.
It's like biting the sleeve of your clothes.
yes
when choreographing
Everyone has costumes, so please hold the sleeve of your clothes and bite.
Please make it look a little sexy
Everyone is buzzing
No, I'll chew on the specially selected costume.
Isn't the third time the most disgusting?
Is it creepy?
shuffle?
There is also a shuffle
cherry blossom star
It's not that unexpected
I don't understand when I'm breastfeeding
I actually did the rehearsal in the gym yesterday.
It's so heart-pounding
I've been an idol for so long
I get really nervous doing it with everyone.
I was talking to everyone yesterday
It's really interesting
Can you see it?
You still don't have makeup on.
It's all about tenses.
Really
I feel bad looking at the monitor
I've been ironing it properly, but it's not working at all.
There are many things
It's beautiful
No way
Ah, that's difficult
I don't know if it's okay though.
Everyone is like this
Resting in various places
Amazing
People who came to staff from the advertising department
There are so many cute idols this time.
Please come
Everyone too
come back
I don't mind going once though
There are a lot of attractive people
They are coming though.
come back
Hey, I don't mind being told that I don't make up like this.
My parents' wife is cute or cute
No? I’m sorry.
cute
kind
Don't be there
Everyone too
In costumes I haven't seen
And my hair is still in progress
Are you on your way?
And I don't have any secret feelings
I really want to buy this compass
On the makeup stage
Even though it will be overtaken
yes
The first person receives the hand
So use Rob
pretty good
yes
Let's do our best
Overcome the tears with a smile
I have lived till today
we actually have quite a problem
It's the strongest
We can do it! We can do anything!
I can go anywhere
I'm sure it'll be okay
Are you okay
It can come true
that's why
We can do it! Don't miss it!
future possibilities
Let's move forward without fear
Shine now
The youth we ran through together
More from here
speed up
Until the next stage
Let's go!
We can do it! Anything
It's the strongest
Good evening
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
oh!
thank you
Boiled dumplings, night toast
I will have a special soup dumpling.
Makeup is perfect too
What punch did you use?
Mr. Kawakami did the Memo Color Punch earlier.
I was blinded by my stomach.
That's so delicious
Because there were many members
I'll stop doing that
Some rehearsals too.
I feel like it's over after I did Gene Pro once.
I'm looking forward to the fans coming to see me this time.
It's okay today, but I wore it.
I only wear chicken wings
Hello
I have a problem
I'm also disappointed
I ate meatballs
I also ate Matsuni
Matsuni is delicious
Delicious no matter when you eat it
I will do my best
I'll enjoy having this
We do it at the opening, but everyone is
The behavior changed little by little
The reaction may change depending on the position.
I don't understand anymore
But it's a little different
It's a little easier to do
But everyone has their own part
The kids behind the scenes
amazing
Very good
I think so.
I am also the momokon finger saxophone
what up?
terrible
My dangerous socks are still a mess
Oh, what's with that finger?
It's dangerous, it's dangerous
Put that away
Oh, what's with the clock of the person holding the microphone?
It's a ruin
I didn't say that name
Until just now, you looked without makeup
Did it become cute?
suddenly
Even just a little bit
I thought it would change so much
It's definitely completely different
I don't think so
Love me no matter what time it is
Hito-chan says
Just now, that idiot
I told you not to blink till the end
Blink your eyes
don't blink
Don't blink till the end
Everyone please watch!
It's finally starting!
The staff is my favorite!
Evelyn
It started out being super cute. happy!
I'm going to Stella Ray.
Yes, progress!
Huh? Hey me.
además
I really like it
Swim Rabbit
It's a rabbit rabbit
He sings Heart Stick Out.
Arlin is here.
Arlin is here today
Everyone is so jumpy and cute
Everyone keeps going
I'll do my best to be the cutest Santoru
I'll do my best
thank you
I recommend Kanten
Kanuki team
Because we're always like uni cars
Recommended
I hope you talk to me
properly
study
please
I'm glad it's green
Ayaka Yasumoto too
in green
If you aim for flowers
There are many green crab misses
That's what it means
It's a gate called
I like Kanuki
thank you
Everyone has a tail
Is it growing a tail?
Is it not growing?
What about headgear?
There are types
cute
I'm happy
I can't see it
It's really cute
cute?
Look at the color of the side dishes
So sparkly
stand out
When is the hardest time?
what?
Danto's performance is the most difficult.
It's the day after tomorrow
the day after tomorrow?
tomorrow?
It's finished
Yes, matching with Pon-chan
Matching Shiba Inu
Shiba Inu dogs
Wan wan wan wan wan
It's smooth
I'll come out first from now on!
Let's go
amazing!
Shining!
cool
I'm so nervous
I was really nervous even though I was in the superlative level just now.
I'm nervous now
get nervous?
I'm nervous
Well, tomorrow's
Tomorrow?
I'm going to go to the station ship Combi Babo.
Now, time
now
Kaname is working hard now.
Ah, Kaname's next day's weather, weather's next day's weather
Now, let me introduce you to my squirrel friends.
oh!
Hello
Hina-chan
Hina-chan's chibita
Ah, that's pretty much it
This is Hina-chan and Ei-chan's chibita.
cute
My stomach is protruding
cute, amazing
cute
Hina-chan
Hinamon's weather
cute
thank you
50 minutes
me
Sorry to bother you. This is Nonoka Kazami.
thank you.
Let's do our best.
I'm Kayai-chan.
what?
you.
I will do my best.
Date, date, I came after being so excited.
happy.
I can see the shoot view of the members, so it's really beautiful.
Because you chose my pants
Is it pants?
Oh, please control me a little.
Acstar is
Acstar is visual
Intro member
Stay with this child
i love containers
I will do my best
to the unit
Let's do our best
ah
cute
thank you
I'm really looking forward to it
Tell me
We are together today too.
We're together
I wonder how everyone was feeling when they watched it
First shoot
Did you take all the wonderful videos and photos?
Yes
That photo is from 2024
You will cherish it as a precious memory.
Yes
thank you
We will never forget this time
We will also cherish
Next time, please stand by.
please
thank you
So the shooting started
The last one has come to an end, but I want it to get even more exciting from here.
Can you speak louder?
I just feel like it's not enough.
Could you please tell me more?
Thank you! Let's keep it that way and keep it exciting!
Next up is this one!
The medley was a lot of fun
Everyone was so close that I felt a little wow.
It was flowing slowly and slowly
The live show that continues today has reached a plateau
That feeling is my world
already!
I
Gather everyone and become one
20 already!
amazing!
yes!
See you again!
Properly!
Nousальнаяуль Invitation
meme
L built up
doctors
nom meeting
thing
or
The blue culture that bloomed
That hand just hurt a little
If you want to get closer to me, spread your hands out.
The voice of pollution is the best
I just met you
I'm super cute right now
Being dumped by you is super cute
This is the maiden's counterattack
I don't know if you've noticed it already, but I'll say it.
I'm so cute right now
The love you started will never end
thank you for your hard work
thank you
That's the end of the first day of staffing.
I wanted to see a lot of promotional V sites now.
Thank you everyone for coming.
thank you for your hard work
Come to the scene and do your best
do your best
I'm going
I can see some of the staff in the picture.
Please squat down
yes cheese
One more yes cheese
thank you
I just can't cry
I was called somehow
Yes, something like that
cute
If you could send me a gift,
Please send me some towels.
It's a gift
Yes, that's why
Give it back
cute
Don't you notice?
It's going to be here
Mayuri is truly a genius and a biscuit
genius?
He's a genius
genius and lucky
Toudon
Udon?
What is it?
Um, flowers, flowers.
Ahahahaha
thank you
He is a genius who was recognized as a genius by lucky people.
bye bye
thank you
yes
So the first day is over.
The first day is about animals.
Starting from being super cute
We all have different animals.
Wear a headband or something
We really covered a lot of things.
It had a lot of content.
There will be 2 performances tomorrow.
I want to do my best tomorrow too.
Don't worry about my strange voice
I'm super energetic
I'll do my best tomorrow too
Everyone is
I went to rehearsal for Mekimeki Gymnastics right now, so
Julia won't appear, so
Julia sent us a summary of the first day.
Bye bye.
The first day of Starbucks, gay development, and the first day of rehearsal have ended.
But this time, I was able to really become friends with everyone at StarPura,
Even when it comes to shooting time,
Even the first-timers said they thought it was cute, which made me really happy.
Right now, I'm taking lots of pictures with everyone, and they're so cute and amazing.
It's fun to play songs that I don't usually play,
I was happy to see it then, but
I am feeling very excited about tomorrow, so
For tomorrow, I'm going to eat, go home early, and go to bed early.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you for watching.